Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Written Work, 24 Linear Feet in 23 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box.; 507 Megabytes in 6,369 digital files.
  - "Seventy-four Characteristics of the World", 1975; cuid35875 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - "Sexing", Undated; cuid35876 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - "Sexing Short-Circuit", Undated; cuid35877 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - "The Sexual Image", 1982; cuid35878 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - "Sexualities, Bindings, Cauterizations, Incandescent Texts", Undated; cuid35879 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - "Shaman", Undated; cuid35880 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - "Shamanic", Undated; cuid35881 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - "Shamanism", Undated; cuid35882 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - "Shamanism and the Flesh of the World", Undated; cuid35883 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - "Shark Attack", July 1982; cuid36107 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - "The Shattering of Worlds", Undated; cuid35884 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - "She Rises", Undated; cuid35885 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - "The Shifty Character in the Kind of Poem That", Undated; cuid35886 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - "Shoreline", Undated; cuid35887 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - "Short-Circuit", Undated; cuid35888 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - "Shtetl", Undated; cuid35889 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - "The Sickness", 1985; cuid35890 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - "Sight: The Recent Work of Marcia Resnick", Undated; cuid35891 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - "Silent Scenarios: Titles", Undated; cuid35892 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - "Singularities", Undated; cuid35893 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - "Skelton in the Closet", Undated; cuid35894 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - "Skitch", Undated; cuid35895 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - "Skull", Undated; cuid35896 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - "Sleazy", Undated; cuid35897 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Sleazy and the Year 3000, Debrisfilm, 1987-1989; cuid35898 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - "Sleazy, Vulgar, Tawdry, Kitsch", Undated; cuid35899 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - "Snapshot", Undated; cuid35900 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - "Snow", Undated; cuid35901 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - "Soho", Undated; cuid35902 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - "Solar Archaeology", 1970; cuid35903 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - "Some Countries", Undated; cuid35904 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - "Some Differences Between Film and Television", Undated; cuid35905 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - "Some Notes on the Block and Diplomatic Language", Undated; cuid35906 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - "Some Notes on Vacuity", Undated; cuid35907 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - "Someone Else", Undated; cuid35908 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - "Someone Just Cited a Jew Again", Undated; cuid35909 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - "Some Statements on Autopornography", Undated; cuid35910 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - "Some Statements on the Phenomenology of Program Space (Phenomenology of Technology)", Undated; cuid35911 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - "Some Texts, Some, in Relation to a Film", Undated; cuid35912 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - "Some Theoretical Concerns", Undated; cuid35913 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - "Somethin' by the Windmill Selm", Undated; cuid35914 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - "Somewhat a Filmscript", Undated; cuid35915 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - "So Neural", Undated; cuid35916 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - "Sondheim Explains Film Povera," Image, March 1985; cuid36117 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - "Song", Undated; cuid35917 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - "Sophia", 2004; cuid35918 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - "The Space and the Time", Undated; cuid35919 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - "Sparks Take it Down", Undated; cuid35920 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - "S.P.E. Saturday, October 15, 11 AM, 1988", cuid35921 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - "Speaking Sex", Undated; cuid35922 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - "Spidee", Undated; cuid35923 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - "Spinthariscope", Undated; cuid35924 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - "Splines of Information Wash Up Against the Debris Left by Text", Undated; cuid35925 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - "Spoliation", Undated; cuid35926 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - "Square", Undated; cuid35927 (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - "Squaredance", Undated; cuid35928 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - "Squeaky Wheel", 1987; cuid35929 (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - "The Squealer!", 1987-1988; cuid35930 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - "Standardized Introduction to the Film(s)", Undated; cuid35931 (Box 49, Folder 58)
  - "State of the Art/Art of the State", 1987; cuid35932 (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - "Statements on Theory", Undated; cuid35933 (Box 49, Folder 60)
  - "Status of the Dreams, Some Dreams, Fevers", Undated; cuid35934 (Box 49, Folder 61)
  - "Stereo", Undated; cuid35935 (Box 49, Folder 62)
  - "(Stereo) (Stereo) (Stereo)", 1984; cuid35936 (Box 49, Folder 63)
  - "Stolen Poem", Undated; cuid35937 (Box 49, Folder 64)
  - "Story", Undated; cuid35938 (Box 49, Folder 65)
  - "The Stress", 1984; cuid35939 (Box 49, Folder 66)
  - "Structure III", Undated; cuid35940 (Box 49, Folder 67)
  - "The Structure of a Theory of Cultural Formations and the Social", Undated; cuid35941 (Box 49, Folder 68)
  - "Structures of Belief", Undated; cuid35942 (Box 49, Folder 69)
  - The Structure of Reality, 1976-1977; cuid35943 (Box 49, Folder 70, Box 50, Folder 1, 2, 3)
  - The Structure of Reality: Evidence of a Theory and Appropriation, 1980; cuid36105 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Structure of Reality Text Plus Appendices, 1977; cuid35944 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - "Studio Problems: 2nd Session", Undated; cuid35945 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - "Style", Undated; cuid35946 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - "Subculture Taxonomy", Undated; cuid35947 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - "Subjectivity and Objectivity", Undated; cuid35948 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - "Subobj", Undated; cuid35949 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - "Sucking-the-Thumb and its Inversion as Inscription", 1976; cuid35950 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - "Suicide", Undated; cuid35951 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - "Suicide Piece; Kill Piece", Undated; cuid35952 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - "Suislawan Text", Undated; cuid35953 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - "Supplement: Irresolution of New Communications Orders", Undated; cuid35954 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - "Supplication and Waiting", Undated; cuid35955 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - "Swansong", Undated; cuid35956 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - "Swollen", Undated; cuid35957 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - "The Swollen Fissure of Painting", Undated; cuid35958 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Syntactical and Semantic Programming, 1978; cuid35959 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Syntactical and Semantic Programming, 1978; cuid35960 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - "The System of Inscriptions", Undated; cuid35961 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - "Systemics of Accumulations", Undated; cuid35962 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - "Tamerlane", Undated; cuid35963 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - "Tangential", Undated; cuid35964 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - "Tao" by Reiner Strasser and Alan Sondheim, 2004; cuid36134 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_14)
    "Tao" is an interactive cinematographic Flash piece, created in collaboration between Alan Sondheim and Reiner Strasser. The musical compositions, which consist of modified shakuhachi, and short video components are by Alan Sondheim.
  - "Tasmanian Punks at the Nowhere Club", Undated; cuid35965 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - "The Tasmanian Work", Undated; cuid35966 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - "Teen Angel's", Undated; cuid35967 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - "The Telegram From a Conceivable Site of War", Undated; cuid35968 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - "Television Piece", 1970; cuid35969 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - "Template Matching for Binary Codes", Undated; cuid35970 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - "Testimony of Love and Death", Undated; cuid35971 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - "Texas", Undated; cuid35972 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Texas Instruments Program Submissions, Undated; cuid35973 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - "(Text)", 1983; cuid35974 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - "Textbook of Thinking", 1991; cuid35975 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Text Files - Poetry, Prose, Notes, and Working Files, 1994-2010; cuid36153 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_33)
  - "Texts" by Alan Sondheim and Geralyn Donahue, 1979; cuid35976 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - "Text to Accompany Recent Films", Undated; cuid35977 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - "Text/Vide: Word Fence", Undated; cuid35978 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - "That 'Self' That 'Thing' is 'Not' ", Undated; cuid35979 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - "Theorem", 1988; cuid35980 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - "Theoretical Work Stemming from The Structure of Reality Reintegrated into Marxist Theoretical Levels", 1978; cuid35981 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - "Theory", 1983; cuid35982 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - "The Theory that Swallowed the World", Undated; cuid35983 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - "Theory of Video", Undated; cuid35984 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - "Them", 1984; cuid35985 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - "The Themes in my Work and its Project", Undated; cuid35986 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - "The Wallpapyr Poems", Undated; cuid35987 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - "There is No One.", 1982; cuid35988 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - "Theses About Jews", Undated; cuid35989 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - "Theses on the Inversion of the Cinema," Millennium Film Journal, 1983; cuid35990 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - "This Cutting Work", Undated; cuid35991 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - "This is All That Can Be Said", Undated; cuid35992 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - "This is How the Film Goes", Undated; cuid35993 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - "This Night of Beautiful Magic", Undated; cuid35994 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - "This Space, Peering Out", Undated; cuid35995 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - "This Way Acconci", Undated; cuid35996 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - "Thomas Chatterton: Introduction to the Notes", 1983; cuid35997 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - "Though", Undated; cuid35998 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - "Those", Undated; cuid35999 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - "The Three Protactions of a New Philosophy", 1990; cuid36000 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - "(Three Short Texts)", Undated; cuid36001 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - "Throat," Art Papers, 1994; cuid36002 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - "Tmo Erotic Filws", 1980; cuid36003 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - "To", Undated; cuid36004 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - "To Carol", Undated; cuid36005 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - "To Energize Such a Word", 1984; cuid36006 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - "To Locate/ To Cross Over", Undated; cuid36007 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - "Tomb", Undated; cuid36008 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - "To Munch", Undated; cuid36009 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - "Toni 8", Undated; cuid36010 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - "To Nira", Undated; cuid36011 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - "Too Late Assassinate", Undated; cuid36012 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - "Torturous Justification", 1972; cuid36013 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - "The Totality of Painting", Undated; cuid36014 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - "Touch and Caress the Beautiful Boundaries of Lipstick on Earth", Undated; cuid36015 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - "Towards a Bibliography", Undated; cuid36016 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - "Towards the Field", Undated; cuid36017 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - "Towards the Fourth Millennium", Undated; cuid36018 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - "Towards a Primary Differentiation Between Film and Video", 1986; cuid36019 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - "Towards a Primary Differentiation Between Film and Video", 1989; cuid36020 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - trAce Online Writing School Residency - Works and Correspondence, 1994-2004; cuid36154 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_34, Box 52, Folder 5)
  - "Trait", Undated; cuid36021 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - "Transcriptions + Annotations", Undated; cuid36022 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - "Transcription From Second Typing Session", Undated; cuid36023 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Translation "From Rafael Alberti: 'Si Mi Voz Muriera en Tierra' ", Undated; cuid36024 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - "Translation", Undated; cuid36025 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Translations of Poems by Federico Garcia Lorca, Undated; cuid36026 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - "Transmission", 1978; cuid36027 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - "Trivial Consequences: Death and Material in the Work of Elma Johnson", Undated; cuid36028 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - "Truth", Undated; cuid36029 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - "Truth", Undated; cuid36030 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - "Truth Emerging in the Hottest Summer", Undated; cuid36031 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - "Turbulence", Undated; cuid36032 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - "Twenty-First Century Script", Undated; cuid36033 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - "Twine. Line.", Undated; cuid36034 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - "Two Circles", Undated; cuid36035 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - "Two Early Poems to Janet", Undated; cuid36036 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - "Two (Four) Views of Niagara", 1979; cuid36037 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - "Two Modes," Meta Ltd., Undated; cuid36038 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - "Two Poems Beginning With Lines From Dante", Undated; cuid36039 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - "Two Short Poems", Undated; cuid36040 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - "Typed Glossolalia: Computer Analysis of Determinism in Man", 1972; cuid36041 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - "Uncertain Theory", Undated; cuid36042 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Untitled Works, Undated; cuid36043 (Box 52, Folder 28, 29, 30, Box 53, Folder 1, 2, 3, 4, Box 54, Folder 1, 2, 3, Box 83, Folder 5)
  - "Untitled Statement for Catalog", Undated; cuid36044 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - "Upon Completing Gorky's 'Life of Matvei Kozhemyakin' ", Undated; cuid36045 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - "UT", Undated; cuid36046 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - "V", Undated; cuid36047 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - "VA", Undated; cuid36048 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - "Vaginality", 1982; cuid36049 (Box 54, Folder 9, 10)
  - "Vaginality: Appendix", Undated; cuid36050 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - "Vaginality: Appendix in Relation to Catastrophe Theory", Undated; cuid36051 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - "(Vaginality) Diachronic: Histories and Originations", Undated; cuid36052 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - "Vaginality: Mathemation", Undated; cuid36053 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - "Vaginality: Remnants of a Physiological Essay", 1982; cuid36054 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - "Verge", Undated; cuid36055 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - "Vignette", Undated; cuid36056 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - "Virga", Undated; cuid36057 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - "Various Titles", Undated; cuid36058 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - "Various Titles (Structures of Reality)," Meta Ltd, Undated; cuid36059 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - "Vascular Trilithon", Undated; cuid36060 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - "Video Texts," Perforations 2, 1991; cuid36061 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - "Village", 1969-1970; cuid36062 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - "Violation Fabric", 1974; cuid36063 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - "Visual Art", Undated; cuid36064 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - "W", 1978; cuid36065 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - "The Wake… The Watch", Undated; cuid36066 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - "Walkingz", Undated; cuid36067 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - "Wall", Undated; cuid36068 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - "Walls Rug [Somewhere]", 1970; cuid36069 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - "War Fever", 1963; cuid36070 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - "Water", 1973; cuid36071 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - "Water", 1988; cuid36072 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - "Waver", Undated; cuid36073 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - "The Way It Works in My Family", Undated; cuid36074 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - The Wayward, 2004; cuid36137 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_17)
  - "Wds. Inscribed Upon a Drawing of a Hand", Undated; cuid36075 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - "We All Make Mistakes: L'Eclisse", Undated; cuid36076 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - "The Weeds", Undated; cuid36077 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - "We Wager Their Resoluteness Surely Overcomes", Undated; cuid36078 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - "What Can I Say?", Undated; cuid36079 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - "What I Believe", Undated; cuid36080 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - "What I Do", Undated; cuid36081 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - "What If", Undated; cuid36082 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - "What I Wish To Write", Undated; cuid36083 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - "What the Engine Does, of the Anorectic Airliner", Undated; cuid36084 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - "When I Found Out About the Children", Undated; cuid36085 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - "When the Chief of the Secret Police Becomes the Leader of the Country", Undated; cuid36086 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - "When the Elders Lose Their True Position", Undated; cuid36087 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - "When We Are Getting Along in This This Time of Our Lives (Filmscript)", Undated; cuid36088 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - "Whistler's Children", 1971; cuid36089 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - William Louis Sørensen, August 1971; cuid36090 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - "The Wind Coming From the Dark Cabinet", Undated; cuid36091 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - "Window", Undated; cuid36092 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - "Within and Without the Thinking of George Stone", 1988; cuid36093 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - "The Woman (Who) Leaves", Undated; cuid36094 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - "The Work of Robert Horvitz in Relation to Inscription Typology", Undated; cuid36095 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - "The Workingman's Ballad of the Return to Decency at the End", Undated; cuid36096 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - "(Working Outline, Sick and Violent Love)", Undated; cuid36097 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - "Working Down from the Universal Set - The Photograph", Undated; cuid36098 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - "Working Up from the Null Set", Undated; cuid36099 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - "Writing", Undated; cuid36100 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - "Writing for the Return of It," Art Papers, 1991; cuid36101 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - "Writings," Tasmanian School of Art, 1982; cuid36102 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - " 'You Do Seem To Deconstruct Power Whenever You Have the Chance, Alan' ", Undated; cuid36103 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - "ZBS", 1976; cuid36104 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - ZZ, 2004; cuid36138 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_18)
- Series II. Visual Art, 7 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes and 4 flat boxes.; 84.3 Gigabytes in 22,499 digital files.
  Series II. Visual Art includes Sondheim's photography as well as drawn, painted, printed, and digitally created work on paper, canvas, and digital files. This series also includes some work by Sondheim's contemporaries and collaborators, such as Mike Metz, Margaret Curtis, Stelarc, and Beth Cannon. Much of Sondeim's work includes sexual content and nudity, and viewer discretion is advised. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - "1 2 3" To-do list with attached photographs, Undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - "4-3-2-0" Hypercube Projection Images, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - 4 x 4 Generated Symmetries, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - "aA" Art Print by Jim Andrews, Undated (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - "A.S. in G.A." Photojournal, Undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Aerial Photographs, circa 1960-1990 (Box 62, Box 63)
  - Aerial Photographs, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Alan Sondheim and David Finkelstein Photographs, Undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Alan Sondheim portrait by V. Elizabeth Turk, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Alan Sondheim Portraits, Undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Art Print from R. Mal (?), 1974 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Artwork by T. Z. for Alan Sondheim, 1983-1986 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - "Azure Bird" Photo Series, 2009; cuid39667 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_35)
  - "Azure Costume" Photo Series, 2009; cuid39668 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_36)
  - "Babble Studies", 1993 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - "Babble Studies (Banners)", 1992 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - "Babble Studies: Knots", 1993 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Balloon Dance Photo Series, 2003; cuid39692 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_61)
  - "Bandage / Bones" Digital Art Series, 2008; cuid39669 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_37)
  - Beth Cannon Artwork, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 8, Box 84, Folder 5)
  - "Bobig" Canvas Piece, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - "Bush League / Bush Whacked" Photo Series, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - "Chart of Activity of Measuring Body Resistance", Undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Cityscape Photographs, circa 1960-1990 (Box 62, Box 63, Box 65, Box 66)
  - "Dance Sphere" Photo/Video Series, 2005-2007; cuid39670 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_38)
  - Descriptions of Photography Series, Undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Digital Art - 3D Modeling and Avatars, 2004-2009; cuid39693 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_62)
  - Digital Art - 3D Scanning, 1999-2009; cuid39694 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_63)
    These images and videos were created with early 3D-Scanning technology including the VIVID-700, Cyrax Laser Scanner, Polhemus motion tracking, and Geomagic Studio.
  - Digital Art - Blender, 2006-2009; cuid39695 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_64)
  - Digital Art - Calculon, 2004-2009; cuid39696 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_65)
  - Digital Art - Image Archive, 1994-2009; cuid39697 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_66)
  - Digital Art - Plotted Images, 1994-2009; cuid39698 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_67)
    3D and 2D graphic images with coordinates, textures, and other properties defined by text files (common formats are .OBJ and .MTL). Both images and their companion files are found here.
  - "Disorders of the Real" Photo / Text Collage, circa 1990 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Dot Matrix Portraits, Undated (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - "The Drawing Together of the Edges of the Page", Undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - "Dreamland" Photo Series, 2008; cuid39671 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_39)
  - Dunlap Tires - Photo Slides, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - "Early Musical Phenakistiscope", Undated (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - "E Hate / An Interruption / A Mob", 1984 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Electron Microscope Photos, circa 1965-1980 (Box 58, Folder 15, Box 59, Folder 11, 12, 13, Box 61, Folder Unknown, Folder 4, Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Emily Cheng Art Print, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - "Equation" Digital Art Series, 2007; cuid39672 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_40)
  - Experimental Photographs, 1970-2008 (Box 58, Folder 16, 17, Box 76, Box 83, Folder 8)
  - "Eye" Photo Series, 2008-2009; cuid39673 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_41)
  - Figure Drawings, Undated (Box 27, Folder 2, 3)
  - Figure Drawings (Damaged Life), Undated (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - "Firefly and Rail" Photo Series, 2008-2009; cuid39674 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_42)
  - "Florida" Photo Series, 2001; cuid39675 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_43)
  - "A Formalism Applicable to the Structure of Most Disciplines" Diagrams, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - "The Formalism Most Probably at the Basis of All Knowledge", 1973 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    Includes a transparency and printed art pieces
  - "Garden" Photo/Video Series, 2006-2007; cuid39676 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_44)
  - Geometric Drawings, 1969-1974 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - "The Generation of Triangles" Drawing, Undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - "Glade" Photo/Video Series, 2001-2003; cuid39677 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_45)
  - "Glass" Photo Series, 2004; cuid39678 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_46)
  - "Gorge" Photo/Video Series, 2004-2006; cuid39679 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_47)
  - "Grl" Photo Series, 2005; cuid39680 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_48)
  - Halifax Flying Club Photographs, Undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - "He His Eyes Closed", Undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - "Hills for Dancing" and "Other Dancers", 1970 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Hogu Art Print, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - "Hollywood (Hollywood)" Photodocumentary Book, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Internet Text Images (Computer print outs), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - "Internet Work" Photo Slides, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - "It's My Bag", Undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Jennifer, Julu, and Nikuko, 1997-2009; cuid39699 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_68)
  - Kara Walker, Crown Camera Photo Slides, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Large Format Photo Negatives, Undated (Box 500)
  - Laura Parker Photographs, 1979-1981 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - "Lights" Photo Series, 2007; cuid39681 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_49)